<?xml version="1.0"?>
<playlist>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/online/mh370-malaysia-pm-wb.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/online/mh370-malaysia-pm-wb.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Malaysia's Prime Minister Najib Razak (2nd L) makes an announcement on the latest development on the missing Malaysia Airlines MH370 plane at Putra World Trade Center in Kuala Lumpur on Monday. Photo: Reuters</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/online/mh370-lost-wb.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/online/mh370-lost-wb.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Relatives of passengers aboard Malaysia Airlines MH370 cry after watching a television broadcast of a news conference, in the Lido hotel in Beijing on Monday. Malaysian Prime Minister Najib Razak has told families of passengers of a missing Malaysian airliner that the plane ended its journey in the southern Indian Ocean. Photo: Reuters</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/online/aus-mh370-boring-fb2.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/online/aus-mh370-boring-fb2.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Journalists look at the monitor of a television camera crew who shot footage onboard a P-3 Orion aircraft of objects in the southern Indian Ocean, during a search of the missing Malaysian Airlines Flight MH370, after returning to RAAF Base Pearce in Bullsbrook, near Perth on Monday. Photo: Reuters</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/online/missing-flight-malaysia.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/online/missing-flight-malaysia.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title></title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/online/malaysia-mh370-pm-wb.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/online/malaysia-mh370-pm-wb.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>A family member of a passenger aboard Malaysia Airlines flight MH370 cries after watching a television broadcast of a news conference, at the Lido hotel in Beijing on Monday. Malaysian Prime Minister Najib Razak has told families of passengers of a missing Malaysian airliner that the plane ended its journey in the southern Indian Ocean. Photo: Reuters</title>
  </slide>
</playlist>
