<?xml version="1.0"?>
<playlist>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin91.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin91.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>A common scenario of the St. Martin Island, PHOTO: SAUD AL FAISAL</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin81.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin81.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Sea going fishing boats. PHOTO: NAZIM UDDIN PRINCE</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin51.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin51.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>The islanders are becoming more dependent on the coastal resources for their subsistence survival by extracting resources that had remained untouched even two decades back. As for example, they are catching fishes from cracks and crevices of rocks, boulders and coral forming areas.  PHOTO: NAZIM UDDIN PRINCE</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin41.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin41.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>High tide at dusk. PHOTO : SAUD AL FAISAL</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin31.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin31.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Fishing is the main profession of the islanders, which is restricted between October and March. Over the decades the islanders and fishing communities from the mainland have depleted the fish stock from within 10 to 20 square kilometers of the Bay of Bengal surrounding the Jinjira Island in an unsustainable way.  PHOTO: SAUD AL FAISAL</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin21_1.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin21_1.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>This fishing practice is unique to our coastal areas, especially Cox&#x2019;s Bazar region. The fishermen set up the net with the onset of the high tide and fishes get trapped at low tide.  PHOTO: NAZIM UDDIN PRINCE</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin1_1.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/st-martin1_1.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>These boats go to the deep sea for fishing. The fishermen bring these to the shore during the dry season to repair and renovate. PHOTO: NAZIM UDDIN PRINCE</title>
  </slide>
</playlist>
