<?xml version="1.0"?>
<playlist>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>The rest of the land belonging to the dormitory remains unoccupied but university students fear it would be gobbled up soon. Photo: Palash Khan </title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city1.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city1.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Gulshanara City, owned by lawmaker and Awami League leader Haji Selim, occupied a part of Tibet Hall of Jagannath University in Old Dhaka. The rest of the land belonging to the dormitory remains unoccupied, inset, but university students fear it would be gobbled up soon.  Photo: Palash Khan</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city2.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city2.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Structures made of corrugated iron sheets now occupy the land where Saidur Rahman Hall and Abdur Rouf Majumder Hall used to stand. Photo: Palash Khan </title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city3.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city3.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>A part of the dormitory Bani Bhaban is now home to two printing presses.  Photo: Palash Khan</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city4.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city4.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>A highrise now stands on the land belonging to Shaheed Shahab Uddin Hall.  Photo: Palash Khan </title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city5.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city5.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>A family claiming to be of a Liberation War martyr has taken over a part of Shaheed Azmal Hossain Hall.  Photo: Palash Khan  </title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city6.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city6.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>The land on which the white building called Crown Market stands used to belong to Crown Bhaban of the university. Photo: Palash Khan </title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city7.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city7.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>There is no sign of Shaheed Anwar Shafique Hall anymore. Six warehouses now occupy the land. Photo: Palash Khan </title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city8.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city8.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>A part of the Shaheed Nazrul Islam Hall is now an orphanage and a madrasa while the rest of the dormitory has been rented out.  Photo: Palash Khan  </title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city9.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city9.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>The now defunct Dhaka city corporation set up Shaheed President Ziaur Rahman School in Bazlur Rahman Hall in 2006.  Photo: Palash Khan </title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city10.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/gulshanara-city10.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>The students of the university managed to recover the land belonging to Habibur Rahman Hall in 2011. Photo: Palash Khan</title>
  </slide>
</playlist>
