<?xml version="1.0"?>
<playlist>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-2_2.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-2_2.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Barbaric attacks on Hindus in Jessore and several northern districts during and after the January 5 parliamentary elections triggered wave of protests across the country. Different organisations on Thursday formed human chains, brought out processions and held rallies, condemning the attacks and demanding arrest and punishment of the culprits. They also called for ensuring security of the minority groups. Photos show demonstrations were also held yesterday in Pabna. Photo: Star</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-3.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-3.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Barbaric attacks on Hindus in Jessore and several northern districts during and after the January 5 parliamentary elections triggered wave of protests across the country. Different organisations on Thursday formed human chains, brought out processions and held rallies, condemning the attacks and demanding arrest and punishment of the culprits. They also called for ensuring security of the minority groups. Photos show demonstrations were also held yesterday in Chandpur. Photo: Star</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-4.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-4.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Barbaric attacks on Hindus in Jessore and several northern districts during and after the January 5 parliamentary elections triggered wave of protests across the country. Different organisations on Thursday formed human chains, brought out processions and held rallies, condemning the attacks and demanding arrest and punishment of the culprits. They also called for ensuring security of the minority groups. Photos show demonstrations were also held yesterday in Chapainawabganj.Photo: Star</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-5.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-5.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Barbaric attacks on Hindus in Jessore and several northern districts during and after the January 5 parliamentary elections triggered wave of protests across the country. Different organisations on Thursday formed human chains, brought out processions and held rallies, condemning the attacks and demanding arrest and punishment of the culprits. They also called for ensuring security of the minority groups. Photos show demonstrations were also held yesterday in Rangpur. Photo: Star</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-6.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-6.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Barbaric attacks on Hindus in Jessore and several northern districts during and after the January 5 parliamentary elections triggered wave of protests across the country. Different organisations on Thursday formed human chains, brought out processions and held rallies, condemning the attacks and demanding arrest and punishment of the culprits. They also called for ensuring security of the minority groups. Photos show demonstrations were also held yesterday in Rajshahi. Photo: Star</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-7.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-7.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Barbaric attacks on Hindus in Jessore and several northern districts during and after the January 5 parliamentary elections triggered wave of protests across the country. Different organisations on Thursday formed human chains, brought out processions and held rallies, condemning the attacks and demanding arrest and punishment of the culprits. They also called for ensuring security of the minority groups. Photos show demonstrations were also held yesterday in Khulna. Photo: Star</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-8.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-8.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Barbaric attacks on Hindus in Jessore and several northern districts during and after the January 5 parliamentary elections triggered wave of protests across the country. Different organisations on Thursday formed human chains, brought out processions and held rallies, condemning the attacks and demanding arrest and punishment of the culprits. They also called for ensuring security of the minority groups. Photos show demonstrations were also held yesterday in Bagerhat. Photo: Star</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-9.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-9.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Barbaric attacks on Hindus in Jessore and several northern districts during and after the January 5 parliamentary elections triggered wave of protests across the country. Different organisations on Thursday formed human chains, brought out processions and held rallies, condemning the attacks and demanding arrest and punishment of the culprits. They also called for ensuring security of the minority groups. Photos show demonstrations were also held yesterday in Pirojpur. Photo: Star</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-10.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/protest-10.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Barbaric attacks on Hindus in Jessore and several northern districts during and after the January 5 parliamentary elections triggered wave of protests across the country. Different organisations on Thursday formed human chains, brought out processions and held rallies, condemning the attacks and demanding arrest and punishment of the culprits. They also called for ensuring security of the minority groups. Photos show demonstrations were also held yesterday in Gopalganj. Photo: Star</title>
  </slide>
</playlist>
