<?xml version="1.0"?>
<playlist>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-1_1.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-1_1.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Police spray coloured water on pro-BNP-Jamaat lawyers using a water-cannon while keeping the Supreme Court's gate closed, barring them from joining the &#x201C;March for Democracy&#x201D; yesterday called by BNP Chairperson Khaleda Zia to force the government to cancel the "one-sided" January 5 parliamentary election. Photo: Anisur rahman, Amran hossain</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-2_1.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-2_1.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>An activist of the ruling Awami League (AL) attacks a rickshaw outside the gate suspecting the passengers to be pro-BNP-Jamaat lawyers. Photo: Anisur Rahman, Amran hossain</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-3.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-3.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>A victim of the clash that followed an attack by some 300 to 400 AL men on the lawyers inside the Supreme Court compound. Photo: Anisur Rahman, Amran hossain</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-4.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-4.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Flames devour a motorcycle set alight by the attackers inside the Supreme Court premises. Photo: Anisur Rahman, Amran hossain</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-5.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-5.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>One of the attackers try to set a bicycle on fire. Photo: Anisur Rahman, Amran hossain</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-6.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-6.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>One elderly attacker uses a slingshot on the lawyers. Photo: Anisur Rahman, Amran hossain</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-8.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-8.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>Supporters of the AL right before police threaten with sticks pro-BNP journalists inside Jatiya Press Club in the capital. Photo: Anisur Rahman, Amran hossain</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-9.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/attack-9.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>A policeman tries to dissuade AL men from attacking the journalists and a generator of theirs brought to power a rally demanding release of Amar Desh acting editor Mahmudur Rahman.Photo: Anisur Rahman, Amran hossain</title>
  </slide>
  <slide>
    <file>/upload/gallery/image/arts/clash-7.jpg</file>
    <thumbnail>/upload/gallery/image/arts/clash-7.jpg</thumbnail>
    <title>BNP supporters retaliate with brick chips during the attack. Photo: Anisur Rahman, Amran hossain</title>
  </slide>
</playlist>
